[English subtitles are available]
[Love you seven times]
[Southern Heavenly Gate]
In ancient times,
the land of the iridescent clouds opened up,
and the six realms were born according to fate,
with one in each position.
The realm I'm in
is the most prominent place
among the six realms.
It's right above these iridescent clouds.
It's the current leader of the six realms,
the supreme
Heaven Realm.
[Heavenly Palace]
[Episode 1]
Our Heaven Realm
[Marriage Pavilion]
is
where all immortals assemble
and gather together.
All the deities
have their own duties.
Among these duties,
there's of course
Lady Wan?
Xiangzi! Xiangzi!
Xiangzi.
My name is Xiangyun. Xiangyun! Xiangyun!
I'm a beautiful lady,
but why do I turn into
a mortal eunuch when you call me?
Xiangzi...
Xiangyun.
[Immortal Li]
Bad news.
The Red Thread Master is crying again.
It’s okay.
Don't cry anymore, sir.
[Master of the Marriage Pavilion, Red Thread Master]
Within seven days,
if I can't
help Immortal Chu Kong get married,
then...
Then what?
Then they'll demolish our Marriage Pavilion.
How can they do that?
Our Marriage Pavilion
shoulders
the hopes of all who's seeking for love in the mortal world.
How can they just demolish it?
Which palace was the immortal envoy from?
How dare they be so arrogant
and bully us?
Watch me break his legs
and seek justice for you, sir.
It was God Haoxuan.
It was God Haoxuan?
You should also be more sensible.
His Holiness has to manage everything every day.
It's inevitable that he said a few harsh words.
Why take it to heart?
Who is this Immortal Chu Kong?
[An immortal of Marriage Pavilion, Jia Yun]
I only heard that
30,000 years ago,
he killed the devil Cang Hai
and protected the peace of the six realms.
But I
have never seen his face before.
You're not the only one.
Many people have never seen
the ancient deity.
He's very mysterious.
Sir, you poor thing.
You've been trying your best to find him a match.
It's been 30,000 years,
but he has never accepted any match.
Even the chances of love
have been avoided by him several times.
This marriage is a tough challenge indeed.
But His Holiness has given an absolute order.
If the Marriage Pavilion were demolished,
I don't want to live anymore.
Sir.
How about this?
Consider
learning to write Fate Books from me.
The Fate Bureau is short of people.
You...
I'm incompetent. I failed my duty.
-I’m sad.
-Sir.
I'm pessimistic and hopeless.
Sir.
Don’t worry.
With this matter,
Xiangzi will definitely help you solve it.
Actually, about this matter, I...
Xiangzi.
You've always been smart.
-Well…
-I knew you would find a solution.
Xiangyun.
Well,
I'll try...
Okay.
This...
Sorry.
By the way,
in ancient times,
30,000 years ago,
there were Moluo, Qilin and Dixiu,
the three divine clans
standing in the world.
Among them, the leader of Moluo, Cang Hai,
had supreme divine power,
and hence was respected as the head of the six realms.
However, according to the Heavenly Divine Oracle,
the empress Cang Hai
will eventually turn into a devil that will exterminate the world.
The people in the six realms were plunged into misery
and were in danger.
But at that moment,
a heroic young man with an imposing demeanor
descended from the sky
and fought with the devil Cang Hai.
This young man sacrificed half of his primordial spirit
and finally annihilated the devil Cang Hai,
and brought peace back to the six realms.
That's horrifying.
The handsome young man I just mentioned
is the male lead of our love auction today.
He is also the most amazing figure in the world.
The royal descendant of Qilin.
The God of War of the six realms.
Immortal Chu Kong.
Why is he so old?
Well...
This can't be it, right?
Sorry.
I took the wrong one.
Immortal Chu Kong.
Even his back is so handsome.
Pipe down.
As they say,
one who loses their position and influence
may be subjected to much indignity.
Today,
this man who has been in the Heaven Realm for years
has finally decided to go to the mortal world.
He's going to fall into the embrace of a fairy.
Why are you hesitating?
What are you waiting for?
This is the perfect chance for you
to be romantically linked with Immortal Chu Kong.
Don't wait.
Today,
you won't make a loss.
I'll offer 30 spirit stones!
50 spirit stones!
I'll offer 100.
I'll offer 150.
I'll offer 201.
I'll offer 300.
Xiangyun, oh Xiangyun.
You sure are clever.
Judging from the situation,
there might
even be some spirit stones left over.
I can bring Red Thread Master and my sisters
on a trip to the other celestial regions.
I'll offer 500.
500?
That much?
Okay.
Everyone,
let's congratulate
-this...
-I'll offer 10,000 spirit stones.
10,000?
Who is that?
And I'll add a Nuwa Stone.
[Princess of the Eastern Sea, Yingshi]
A Nuwa Stone?
Why?
Is it not enough?
It's enough.
Of course it's enough.
Princess Yingshi.
From now on,
Immortal Chu Kong is yours.
Let's all congratulate
Princess Yingshi.
Congratulations, Princess.
[Mount Moluo]
Lord Protector, I'm here to report that
we've finally found the ancient artifact, Nuwa Stone.
It's now in the Heaven Realm.
As long as we get the Nuwa Stone,
we will have a chance to revive the monarch Cang Hai.
Lord Protector.
[Protector of the Moluo Divine Clan, Jin Lian]
We are always on standby.
The Heaven Realm killed my monarch,
slaughtered my people,
and regarded my Moluo Divine Clan
as a threat to the six realms.
Now,
Monarch Cang Hai is about to return.
It's been 30,000 years.
[Guard of the Moluo Divine Clan, Xie Feng]
I've been waiting for this moment for 30,000 years.
[Southern Heavenly Gate]
Your Holiness.
The Moluo Clan is approaching aggressively.
[Immortal Sun]
I'm afraid
the God of War has to come forward.
In order to restore his primordial spirit,
Chu Kong is currently in seclusion.
If we force him out,
I'm afraid it might backfire.
[Heavenly Emperor Haoxuan]
But now the Heaven Realm
is in danger.
The safety of everyone depends on him alone.
We can't wait any longer.
This way.
I remember clearly that they were here.
[Ancient God of War, Chu Kong]
You...
Jin Lian.
I just took a nap,
and you've managed to make the Heaven Realm so lively.
Indeed,
you're unbelievably stupid.
Enough with the nonsense.
Bind.
Hurry!
Keep that safe.
The Book of Marriage Prayers is the secret of the Heavenly Palace.
Jin Qilin?
Chu Kong?
Heaven and earth are turned upside down
right in front of us.
Could it be...
that he is... the God of War, Immortal Chu Kong?
[Chief of the Fate Bureau, Goddess of Fate]
The Heavenly Divine Oracle?
[Cang Hai will be resurrected within a thousand years]
Within 1,000 years,
Cang Hai will be resurrected.
Cang Hai will be resurrected?
Really?
Your Holiness.
If the calculations of the Fate Bureau are right,
the Heavenly Divine Oracle says that
the six realms
will face a calamity.
Your Holiness.
30,000 years ago,
although Immortal Chu Kong
personally killed that demon Cang Hai,
he lost half of his primordial spirit
and even lost all his memories
before and after that battle.
He paid a heavy price.
This time, he failed in his seclusion
and his primordial spirit was damaged.
Besides, after the battle with Jin Lian,
the recovery is becoming increasingly sluggish.
With the current divine power of the God of War,
I'm afraid...
A thousand years are merely a moment's time.
In that case,
isn't the disaster
of the six realms near?
What should we do?
Everyone, don't worry.
Even if the devil comes back to life,
I’m confident I can kill him again.
In that case,
everyone,
why are you so worried?
There is the God of War Chu Kong in our Heaven Realm.
There's no need to be afraid of that devil.
So,
dismiss.
Chu Kong.
It's been 30,000 years.
You've tried all kinds of methods,
but your primordial spirit hasn't fully recovered.
In these 81 hardships,
you're only without
the love tribulation.
Love tribulation?
I know you hate romantic love the most.
But now,
this is the only method you haven't tried.
I
have arranged for the Marriage Pavilion to help find you a match.
If you can overcome this love tribulation,
it might help you restore your primordial spirit.
Don't worry, Your Divinity.
I won't let anything happen to the six realms.
Chu Kong.
I'm
still worried about you.
Xiangyun.
The Red Thread Master and Immortal Li are worried about you.
I'm fine.
By the way,
was that yellow-haired fellow just now
really the God of War of the six realms,
Immortal Chu Kong?
Didn't you say
he's an ancient immortal
who's over 50,000 years old?
I heard that he knows the magic for eternal youth,
which means his magic prowess is unfathomable.
Who would have thought
a 50,000-year-old man would be able
to maintain himself so well?
Are you really going to
set the two of them up?
Well,
you heard what the Red Thread Master said
the last time.
If we can't help
Immortal Chu Kong find a match,
our Marriage Pavilion will be gone.
It's a pity that my Nuwa Stone
left me
before I could appreciate it properly.
Instead of being heartbroken about external belongings,
you'd better think about
how to tie this relationship.
With His Divinity's divine power,
perhaps when you
just get close to him,
you'll be...
What
silly plans are you thinking about again?
Don't do anything stupid.
How can you call a good deed stupid?
We just need to keep it a secret from Red Thread Master.
Wait for my good news.
Xiangyun.
What are you doing?
You're so childish.
How dare you steal an ancient magical artifact?
This is the treasure of your Pavilion.
If the Red Thread Master finds out you touched his treasure,
he will cry and make a scene again.
To deal with the ancient God of War,
we must use ancient magical artifacts.
I heard that
even if there's zero possibility
for two people who are not meant to be,
as long as they are connected by this Love Knot,
they'll definitely be tied into
an unbreakable bond of love.
An ancient magical artifact?
Since we're here,
I'll
help you check this out at least.
Ouch, it's hot!
Something is wrong with this thing.
Something is wrong?
No.
I-I just...
It-It-It...
When is Immortal Chu Kong the most relaxed?
You should know that.
[Star Platform]
You can try your luck at the Star Platform.
That is the place where the spiritual power of Heaven and Earth is the strongest.
His Divinity occasionally sleeps at the Star Platform
to absorb the spiritual power and restore his primordial spirit.
Greetings, Your Divinity.
Why is someone from the Marriage Pavilion
here at the Star Platform?
I...
am here to repay you for saving my life.
Really?
The way you're repaying me
is really interesting.
You were by my side just now.
If I didn’t stop you…
what were you trying to do?
I-I...
I was...
Who do you think you are?
How dare you act recklessly in front of me.
Please spare my life.
I'm innocent.
I just saw that you were alone
and seemed lonely.
So I wanted to do something
for you within my capabilities.
That's why I wanted to arrange a blissful marriage
for you.
As for why
I almost touched your face just now,
it's because I thought
you seemed familiar
and I had a feeling of reunion.
Familiar?
Stand up.
Raise your head
for me.
I finally found you.
Xiangyun.
You auctioned my love
and disregarded the laws of heaven
and violated the divine dignity.
Pass my message.
The Marriage Pavilion...
Tear it down.
The Marriage Pavilion can't be destroyed in my hands.
If I fulfill His Holiness' order
and make a contribution,
I wonder if he'll spare the Marriage Pavilion.
Whatever.
I'll risk it.
Your Divinity.
I...
This...
I don't know
how to untie this Love Knot.
I...
I know how to.
Your Divinity.
Are you going to cut off my hand
or slash me?
What do you think?
Wait.
Don't come over.
If you come any closer,
I'll jump.
Your Divinity, consider it carefully.
If I jump into this Mortal World Well,
in the vastness of the six realms,
you won't be able to find me.
If you jump into the broken Mortal World Well,
and fall into the Mysterious Realm,
or the Boundless Realm,
you could very well die.
Don't you know?
Even if I fall into the Boundless Realm or the Mysterious Realm,
I won't let you stop me.
I... Don't move!
I'm really going to jump.
Then jump.
I...
Your Divinity.
I suddenly thought it over.
I think there might be some misunderstandings between us.
I can explain.
It's not necessary.
Thank goodness.
It's the mortal world.
How could I
actually control
these two little cute paws?
Wait.
Have I…
become a tiger after getting into a tribulation?
A boar?
It's you?
Immortal Chu Kong?
Immortal Chu Kong
actually turned into
an ugly boar!
You...
Pig Kong?
Sorry.
Chu Kong.
Immortal Chu Kong.
Wait for me!
Your Divinity.
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone
that you became
a boar.
My glorious reputation
cannot be tarnished.
I have to
erase
her
memory!
Oh no.
I forgot that during tribulations,
immortals can't use their magic.
Looks like
I have to be his bootlick
to stay alive.
Your Divinity.
Go.
Go away.
Don't come near me.
Your Divinity.
What are you doing?
Don’t follow me.
I need to go back.
Be careful, Your Divinity!
How dare you!
Are you afraid that you won't die tragically enough
when you go back?
My leg is cramping.
Stay still.
Let me pull you up.
Let's have a look.
Let's go.
Perfect timing.
In tribulations,
when my mortal body dies,
I'll be returned to my immortal self.
Don't be afraid, Your Divinity.
I'll protect you with my life.
Go away.
Don't ruin my plan.
Don't worry.
I won't let them hurt you.
Can you...
Your Divinity.
Calm down.
Get lost!
Your Divinity.
Your Divinity, don't go over there.
Don't make trouble for me.
Immortal Chu Kong.
Be good.
Don't try to be a hero.
It's time for me to show my loyalty.
Your Divinity.
You should believe
that I'm loyal to you now.
You mess things up
all the time!
When I return to Heaven Realm,
I'll settle the score with you.
Isn't this
too disgraceful?